Back to me new video
how to cancel the payment bank atal pension yojana insurance premium, I will
tell you three tricks which will work
for you, let's start this video
directly, like if
you open an Airtel payment bank then
what will be the insurance there, 145 rupees
or 45 for some, 108 rupees for some, 112
paise for some, what happens in the deduction that happens,
after deducting your premium it
goes into your insurance, so
after doing it you are given insurance in it,
someone's 2 lakh or someone's 4 lakh, according to which
you have taken insurance, it would have been done accordingly, so
we are going to tell you how to cancel that insurance, so
first of all what you have to do is
open the chrome browser,
as you open it, what do you have to do here, let's search here,
then we will take it,
like what do you have to do, Airtel payment
bank insurance customer care number,
click on it here, as if you
click here, a number will appear at the top,
you have to go down and scroll a little,
insurance premium payment
online  On Health and Livelihood,
you have to click on it, if you click here, an
interface like this will appear in front of you, so what you have to do
here is to
scroll a little, if you
scroll here, then see here, you will see many
services in it, but you do
not have to click on the insurance premium here, you have to click on the
Atal Pension Yojana which is written,
as if you will click here,
after clicking,
see, a number will be shown in front of you,
scroll a little and
see here, the number is showing here, the
contact number is also there and this is the WhatsApp number and this is the
calling number, click on this number, it
is registered with the G number, click on that number, it
is registered with the payment bank number, click on it from here and say
that I have an insurance,
we want to band that insurance, then what will happen to you there,
Aadhar card and PAN card will be
asked and your full details will be asked,
full address etc. will be asked,
you tell us that process, this is the first
step which no one might have told, now
what is the second step again  You have to go
to Google, it will appear here, so
what will you have to do after coming here, let's go back,
like
come here, then you have to search the same thing,
what number will you get here,
an Airtel customer dial number 400, on this number
you have to dial the number of 400,
like dial it, after entering your P etc. everything, it will go to
customer care
and from there you can solve this program,
tell him that we have to cancel the insurance, from
there he will make the claim, the
insurance person will call you directly on that
number, he will cancel it, then
what is the third number here, now
see here, Airtel Payment Bank dial number is
8800 68
68806, this is the number, these are three numbers, you can cancel the
insurance by talking on all three numbers, there will be no problem
easily,
you
apply the process, it will 100% work and we will also cancel the process, but
I did not have any proof,
but it is 100% real that this is for you people  If you
do then thanks for watching this video
by